<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields xmlns:xd="http://www.pnp-software.com/XSLTdoc"
        xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2002/07/owl#"
        xmlns:owl="http://www.w3.org/2002/07/owl#"
        xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#">
   <field>
      <id>Article</id>
      <def>A written work published in a print or electronic medium. It may be for the purpose of propagating the news, research results, academic analysis or debate.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Book</id>
      <def>A written or printed work consisting of pages glued or sewn together along one side and bound in covers.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BookChapter</id>
      <def>One of the main divisions of a book. Chapters can be numbered or titled or both.

source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chapter_(books)</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BookReview</id>
      <def>A critical appraisal of a book published in a newspaper or magazine.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BookSection</id>
      <def>Any of the more or less distinct parts into which a book is or may be divided or from which it is made up.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Booklet</id>
      <def>A small, thin book with paper covers, typically giving information on a particular subject.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Chapter</id>
      <def>One of the main divisions of a piece of writing of relative length, such as a book of prose, poetry, or law. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Dataset</id>
      <def>A collection of related sets of information that is composed of separate elements but can be manipulated as a unit by a computer.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Dissertation</id>
      <def>A long essay on a particular subject, especially one written for a university degree or diploma.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EditedBook</id>
      <def>A book that features articles or other material on the same subject but by different authors collected together in one book by an editor.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EditedVolume</id>
      <def>A collection of scholarly or scientific chapters written by different authors. The chapters in an edited volume are original works. Alternative terms for edited volume are contributed volume, edited collection and multiauthor volume.

source: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edited_volume </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Essay</id>
      <def>A short piece of writing on a particular subject.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Image</id>
      <def>A representation of a thing by a person in art or an impression obtained by a device</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Journal</id>
      <def>A newspaper or magazine that deals with a particular subject or professional activity.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Leaflet</id>
      <def>A printed sheet of paper containing information or advertising and usually distributed free.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Letter</id>
      <def>A written, typed, or printed communication, sent in an envelope by post or messenger.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Magazine</id>
      <def>A periodical publication containing articles and illustrations, often on a particular subject or aimed at a particular readership.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Monograph</id>
      <def>A detailed written study in the form of an essay or book, of a single specialized subject or an aspect of it, usually by a single author.

Librarians consider a monograph to be a nonserial publication complete in one volume (book) or a finite number of volumes.

source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Monograph</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Newsletter</id>
      <def>A regularly distributed publication that is generally about one main topic of interest to its subscribers</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Newspaper</id>
      <def>A printed publication (usually issued daily or weekly) consisting of folded unstapled sheets and containing news, articles, advertisements, and correspondence.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Pamphlet</id>
      <def>A small booklet or leaflet containing information or arguments about a single subject.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Paper</id>
      <def>An essay or dissertation, especially one read at an academic lecture or seminar or published in an academic journal.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Periodical</id>
      <def>A magazine or newspaper published at regular intervals.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PolicyBrief</id>
      <def>A concise summary of a particular issue, the policy options to deal with it, and some recommendations on the best option. 

It is aimed at government policymakers and others who are interested in formulating or influencing policy.

Policy briefs can take different formats. A typical format is a single A4 sheet (210 x 297 mm), containing perhaps 700 words. It has an attractive design, and may have one or more photograph. Longer briefs (up to 8 pages, or 3,000 words) and other formats are also possible.

source: http://www.fao.org/docrep/014/i2195e/i2195e03.pdf</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Publication</id>
      <def>A book or journal issued for public sale.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Report</id>
      <def>An account given of a particular matter, especially in the form of an official document, after thorough investigation or consideration by an appointed person or body.

source: http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/english/report</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Review</id>
      <def>A critical appraisal of a book, play, film, etc. published in a newspaper or magazine.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Series</id>
      <def>A set of books, periodicals, or other documents published in a common format or under a common title.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Thesis</id>
      <def>A dissertation involving personal research, written by a candidate for a university degree.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>WrittenWork</id>
      <def>A creative work in the written form.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>CreativeWork</id>
      <def>A work that is a distinct intellectual or artistic creation and is the product of creative effort.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Instance</id>
      <def>An example or single occurrence of a manifestation of a creative work.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Manifestation</id>
      <def>A version or incarnation of a creative work</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Theme</id>
      <def>An idea that recurs in or pervades a work of art or literature.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Buyer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DataDeposition</id>
      <def>The activity of depositing data, ie putting data in a specific place for safekeeping.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DataPackage</id>
      <def>A set amount of data.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DataSilo</id>
      <def>A data storage unit that operates in isolation from others.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DataSiloGeneral</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Depositor</id>
      <def>The role of a person who gives or entrusts something to an entity for safekeeping.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Fund</id>
      <def>A sum of money saved or made available for a particular purpose.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Grant</id>
      <def>A sum of money given by a government or other organization for a particular purpose.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Owner</id>
      <def>The role of a person who owns something, ie that someone or something belongs or relates to the person mentioned.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>OwnershipActivity</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Payee</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Payer</id>
      <def>The role of a person who pays money for something</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Payment</id>
      <def>An amount paid or payable.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PaymentActivity</id>
      <def>The activity or process of paying someone or something or of being paid</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Seller</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Transaction</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Baptism</id>
      <def>The Christian religious rite of sprinkling water on to a person’s forehead or of immersing them in water, symbolizing purification or regeneration and admission to the Christian Church. In many denominations, baptism is performed on young children and is accompanied by name-giving.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BaptismalCandidate</id>
      <def>The role of a person who is admitted to membership of a Christian church.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Bishop</id>
      <def>A senior member of the Christian clergy, usually in charge of a diocese and empowered to confer holy orders.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Chapter</id>
      <def>The governing body of a religious community</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Church</id>
      <def>A particular Christian organization with its own clergy, buildings, and distinctive doctrines.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Confessee</id>
      <def>The role of a person who repents their sins and (in the Christian Church) seeks forgiveness from God.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Confessor</id>
      <def>The role of a priest who hears confessions and gives absolution and spiritual counsel</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ConfirmationCandidate</id>
      <def>The role of a person who is confirmed during the religious rite or sacrament of confirmation</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Congregation</id>
      <def>A group of people assembled for religious worship.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Council</id>
      <def>An advisory, deliberative, or administrative body of people formally constituted and meeting regularly.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DisqualifiedFromEcclesiasticalOffice</id>
      <def>Activity where a person is disqualified ie declared ineligible for an ecclesiastical office.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DisqualifiedFromOffice</id>
      <def>The role of a person who has been declared ineligible for an office because of an offence or infringement</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EcclesiasticalAdministrativeOffice</id>
      <def>An administrative position of authority or service in an ecclesiastical organisation.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EcclesiasticalOffice</id>
      <def>A position of authority or service in an ecclesiastical organisation.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EcclesiasticalOrganisation</id>
      <def>An organisation related to the Christian Church.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Godchild</id>
      <def>The role of a person who is presented at baptism by a godparent who promises to take responsibility for their religious education.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Godfather</id>
      <def>A male godparent</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Godmother</id>
      <def>A female godparent</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Godparent</id>
      <def>The role of a person who presents a person at baptism and promises to take responsibility for their religious education.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>HoldEcclesiasticalOffice</id>
      <def>The activity of a person holding an ecclesiastical office, i.e. a position of authority or service, typically one of a public nature.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Member</id>
      <def>The role of an agent belonging to a particular group</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MembershipEcclesiasticalBody</id>
      <def>The activity of a person being a member of an ecclesiastical body.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Minister</id>
      <def>A member of the clergy, especially in the Presbyterian and Nonconformist Churches.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MonasticOffice</id>
      <def>A position of authority or service in a monastic organisation.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Office</id>
      <def>A position of authority or service, typically one of a public nature</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Officiant</id>
      <def>The role of a person who performs a religious rite or presides over a religious service or ceremony.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Ordination</id>
      <def>The action of making (someone) a priest or minister; confer holy orders.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Preach</id>
      <def>Deliver a sermon or religious address to an assembled group of people, typically in church.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Priest</id>
      <def>An ordained minister of the Catholic, Orthodox, or Anglican Church, authorized to perform certain rites and administer certain sacraments. http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/english/priest</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Religion</id>
      <def>A particular system of faith and worship.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ReligiousConfession</id>
      <def>Confession is the acknowledgment of sin (or one's sinfulness) or wrongs. It is a religious practice in a number of faith traditions.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ReligiousConfirmation</id>
      <def>Confirmation is a rite of initiation in several Christian denominations, normally carried out through anointing, the laying on of hands, and prayer, for the purpose of bestowing the Gift of the Holy Spirit.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ReligiousConversion</id>
      <def>The adoption, wholesale, of a set of beliefs identified with one particular religious denomination to the exclusion of others. Religious conversion marks a transformation of religious identity and is symbolized by special rituals.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Religious_conversion</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ReligiousConvert</id>
      <def>The role of a person who participates in a conversion of religious identity</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Synod</id>
      <def>An assembly of the clergy and sometimes also the laity in a diocese or other division of a particular Church.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AcademicSubject</id>
      <def>A branch of knowledge studied or taught in a school, college, or university.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Author</id>
      <def>A writer of a book, article, or document.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AwardingBody</id>
      <def>The role of an agent that gives an award.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ClassList</id>
      <def>A list of the candidates who have taken an examination, showing the class or mark achieved by each.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ClassRegistration</id>
      <def>A matriculation activity that involves adding candidates who have taken an examination, to a class list, showing the class or mark achieved by each.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Disputation</id>
      <def>Formal academic debate  
source: http://www.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/english/disputation

In the scholastic system of education of the Middle Ages, disputations (in Latin: disputationes, singular: disputatio) offered a formalized method of debate designed to uncover and establish truths in theology and in sciences. Fixed rules governed the process: they demanded dependence on traditional written authorities and the thorough understanding of each argument on each side.
source https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Disputation

Also see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Praeses#Old_German_academic_use </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EducationalPost</id>
      <def>A post in an educational organization.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Entry</id>
      <def>An item written or printed in a diary, list, account book, or reference book.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Graduate</id>
      <def>A person who has successfully completed a course of study or training, especially a person who has been awarded an undergraduate or first academic degree.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Lecturer</id>
      <def>A person who gives lectures, especially (Brit.) as an occupation at a university or college of higher education.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>List</id>
      <def>A number of connected items or names written or printed consecutively, typically one below the other.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Matriculant</id>
      <def>A person who has matriculated or been registered on a list or roll, usually at a school.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Matriculation</id>
      <def>From https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Matriculation:

Matriculation, in the broadest sense, means to be registered or added to a list, from the Latin matricula – little list. The most common meaning refers to the formal process of entering a university or of becoming eligible to enter by fulfilling certain academic requirements.

In Scottish heraldry, a matriculation is a registration of armorial bearings.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MatriculationRegister</id>
      <def>An official list or record of names of people who have participated in the activity of matriculation at a university, the formal process of entering a university or of becoming eligible to enter by fulfilling certain academic requirements.

source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Matriculation</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Mentor</id>
      <def>An experienced and trusted adviser.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PersonalTestimony</id>
      <def>A solemn written or oral statement as to the truth of a matter.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PersonalTestimonyActivity</id>
      <def>The activity of a solemn written or oral statement as to the truth of a matter.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Praeses</id>
      <def>A person who is the faculty moderator of an academic disputation, normally proposing a thesis and participating in the ensuing disputation</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Professor</id>
      <def>A university academic of the highest rank.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ProfessorExtraordinary</id>
      <def>In Germany, post of professor without a university chair. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ProfessorOrdinary</id>
      <def>Post of Professor in Germany</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PromotionToDegree</id>
      <def>The receiving or conferring of an academic degree.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Rector</id>
      <def>The head of certain universities, colleges, and schools.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Register</id>
      <def>An official list or record of names or items.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Respondent</id>
      <def>A person or organization who makes an answer to the courts pursuant to an application for redress (usually in an equity proceeding) or a candidate for a degree who defends or opposes a thesis provided by the praeses in an academic disputation</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Student</id>
      <def>A person who is studying at a university or other place of higher education.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Study</id>
      <def>The devotion of time and attention to acquiring knowledge on an academic subject, especially by means of books.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Teacher</id>
      <def>The role of a person who imparts knowledge to or instructs someone as to how to do something.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Teaching</id>
      <def>The activity of giving instruction, especially in an elementary or secondary school or a university.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>TeachingInstitution</id>
      <def>An organisation where the activity of imparting knowledge to or instructing (someone) as to how to do something is conducted.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Testifier</id>
      <def>A person who gives a testimony, a solemn written or oral statement as to the truth of a matter.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Tutor</id>
      <def>A private teacher, typically one who teaches a single pupil or a very small group</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>University</id>
      <def>A high-level educational institution in which students study for degrees and academic research is done.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>UniversityMatriculation</id>
      <def>The formal process of entering a university or of becoming eligible to enter by fulfilling certain academic requirements.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>APCPaymentStatus</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Agent</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Article</id>
      <def>A piece of writing included with others in a newspaper, magazine, or other publication.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Author</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Book</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BookSection</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ConferenceEvent</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ConferenceItem</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ConferencePaper</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Creator</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Data</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DiscussionPaper</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Format</id>
      <def>A defined structure for the processing, storage, or display of data

the medium in which a sound recording is made available

the shape, size, and presentation of a book or periodical</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>HostPublication</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Journal</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>JournalArticle</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>OpenAccessStatus</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Person</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PressArticle</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Publication</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ResearchObject</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ResearchProject</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Role</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Series</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Source</id>
      <def>A place, person, or thing from which something originates or can be obtained.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Thesis</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>WorkingPaper</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AuthoringActivity</id>
      <def>Activity that involves the writing of a book, article or document.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ContributionActivity</id>
      <def>Activity that involves the contiribution of something by a person or thing</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>CreationActivity</id>
      <def>Activity that brings something into existence.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Dedication</id>
      <def>An inscription or form of words dedicating a building, book, etc. to a person or deity.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DedicationActivity</id>
      <def>An activity that involves an address or inscription (of a literary work, for example) to another as a mark of respect or affection</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EditingActivity</id>
      <def>Activity of preparing written material for publication by correcting, condensing, or otherwise modifying it.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>HoldOfficeLearnedOrganisation</id>
      <def>The state of holding office in a learned organisation.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LearnedActivityRole</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MembershipLearnedOrganisation</id>
      <def>Membership of a learned organisation</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>OfficeLearnedOrganisation</id>
      <def>An office in a learned organisation</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PrintingActivity</id>
      <def>Activity that involves the production of books, newspapers or other printed materials.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PublishingActivity</id>
      <def>The activity of preparing and issuing books, journals and other materials for sale.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Research</id>
      <def>An activity involving the systematic investigation into and study of materials and sources in order to establish facts and reach new conclusions.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ReviewActivity</id>
      <def>An activity involving the formal assessment of something with the intention of instituting change if necessary</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>TranslationActivity</id>
      <def>An activity involving the translation of words or text from one language into another.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BiographicalLocationRole</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Country</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Displacement</id>
      <def>The enforced departure of people from their homes, typically because of war, persecution, or natural disaster.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Emmigration</id>
      <def>The activity of leaving one's own country to settle permanently in another; moving abroad.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Exile</id>
      <def>The state of being barred from one's native country, typically for political or punitive reasons.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Immigration</id>
      <def>The activity of of coming to live permanently in a foreign country.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Residence</id>
      <def>The activity of living in a particular place.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Travel</id>
      <def>The activity of making a journey, typically of some length.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Visit</id>
      <def>The activity of going to see a person or place as a guest, tourist, etc.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Actor</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Alchemist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Ambassador</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Anatomist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Antiquary</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Apothecary</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Architect</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Artisan</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Assistant</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Astrologer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Astronomer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Barrister</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Biographer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Bookseller</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Chemist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Classicist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>CourtPhysician</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Diplomat</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DisqualificationFromOffice</id>
      <def>Activity declaring (someone) ineligible for an office because of an offence or infringement</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Doctor</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Dramatist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Editor</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>EducationalTheorist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Employment</id>
      <def>The activity of having paid work.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Engraver</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GovernmentOfficial</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Herbalist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Historian</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Iatrochemist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Illustrator</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>InstrumentMaker</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Inventor</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Judge</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Juror</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Keeper</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Lawyer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LearnedOrganization</id>
      <def>A formal organization that facilitates the learning of its members</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LegalAdvocate</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LegalPost</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LetterCarrier</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Librarian</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Linguist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Logician</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Mathematician</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MedicalPost</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MedicalPractitioner</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MembershipProfessionalBody</id>
      <def>Membership of a person to a professional body</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Merchant</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MilitaryOfficer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Musician</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>NaturalHistorian</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>NaturalPhilosopher</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Naturalist</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Nonjuror</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Notary</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Office</id>
      <def>A post that is a position of authority or service, typically one of a public nature.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Orator</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Painter</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Philosopher</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Physician</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Poet</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PoliticalGroup</id>
      <def>A formal organization that has a common political purpose.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Politician</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>President</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Printer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ProfessionalBody</id>
      <def>A nonprofit formal organization seeking to further a particular profession, the interests of individuals engaged in that profession, and the public interest.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Publisher</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Reviewer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Scholar</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Sculptor</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Secretary</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Soldier</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Solicitor</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Surgeon</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Theologian</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Translator</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Treasurer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Writer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>HoldOffice</id>
      <def>The activity of a person holding a public office.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Conference</id>
      <def>A formal meeting of people with a shared interest, typically one that takes place over several days.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ConferenceItem</id>
      <def>A digital object that has been produced for, or as a result of, a conference.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ConferencePaper</id>
      <def>A paper presented at an academic conference for researchers to present and discuss their work.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ConferencePoster</id>
      <def>A poster that has the purpose of presenting research information by an individual or representatives of research teams at a conference with an academic or professional focus. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DiscussionPaper</id>
      <def>A paper that includes research but tend to be shorter and more selective in its approach, and more analytical and critical, than a research paper.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Essay</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>JournalArticle</id>
      <def>An article that is published in a journal.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Patent</id>
      <def>A patent protects new inventions and covers how things work, what they do, how they do it, what they are made of and how they are made.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PatentApplication</id>
      <def>A request pending at a patent office for the grant of a patent for the invention described and claimed by that application.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PostPrintArticle</id>
      <def>An article that is in the final form post printing of the publication in which it is published.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PrePrintArticle</id>
      <def>An article in the form before it is published.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PressArticle</id>
      <def>A written or recorded communication directed at members of the news media for the purpose of announcing something ostensibly newsworthy.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ResearchPaper</id>
      <def>A paper that is intended to uncover a wide variety of sources on a given topic.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Essay</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>TechnicalReport</id>
      <def>A report that describes the process, progress, or results of technical or scientific research or the state of a technical or scientific research problem. It might also include recommendations and conclusions of the research.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>WorkingPaper</id>
      <def>A preliminary scientific or technical paper. Often, authors will release working papers to share ideas about a topic or to elicit feedback before submitting to a peer reviewed conference or academic journal. Working papers are often the basis for related works, and may in themselves be cited by peer-review papers.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Adult</id>
      <def>A person who is fully grown or developed.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BiologicalSex</id>
      <def>Reproductive function of humans and most other living things.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Child</id>
      <def>A young human being below the age of puberty or below the legal age of majority.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Female</id>
      <def>The biological sex that can bear offspring or produce eggs, distinguished biologically by the production of gametes (ova) which can be fertilized by male gametes.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Male</id>
      <def>The biological sex that produces gametes, especially spermatozoa, with which a female may be fertilized or inseminated to produce offspring.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Man</id>
      <def>An adult human male.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Woman</id>
      <def>An adult human female.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Adoption</id>
      <def>A process whereby a person assumes the parenting for another and, in so doing, permanently transfers all rights and responsibilities, along with filiation, from the biological parent or parents.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AdoptiveFather</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AdoptiveMother</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Ancestor</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Aunt</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Birth</id>
      <def>The start of life as a physically separate being.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BirthFather</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BirthMother</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Brother</id>
      <def>Definition: A man or boy in relation to other sons and daughters of his parents</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>BrotherInLaw</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Cousin</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>CousinInLaw</id>
      <def>A cousin-in-law is the spouse of an individual's cousin or the cousin of one's spouse.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Daughter</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Death</id>
      <def>The activity of dying or being killed; the end of the life of a person or organism.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Deceased</id>
      <def>A person who is recently dead.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Descendent</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DoubleCousin</id>
      <def>Double cousins arise when two siblings of one family reproduce with two siblings of another family. The resulting children are related to each other through both of their parents and are thus doubly related. Double first cousins share both sets of grandparents in common and have twice the degree of consanguinity of ordinary first cousins. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>FamilyRole</id>
      <def>Role of an individual within a family unit. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Father</id>
      <def>Definition: The family role of a man in relation to his child or children</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>FatherInLaw</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>FirstCousin</id>
      <def>The children of two siblings.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>FirstCousinOnceRemoved</id>
      <def>Two people for whom a first cousin relationship is one generation removed.
The child of one's first cousin; also the first cousin of one's parent.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>FirstCousinTwiceRemoved</id>
      <def>Two people for whom a first cousin relationship is two generations removed.
The grandchild of one's first cousin; also the first cousin of one's grandparent.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GrandParent</id>
      <def>A parent of one's father or mother; a grandmother or grandfather.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Grandchild</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Granddaughter</id>
      <def>A daughter of one's son or daughter.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Grandfather</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Grandmother</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Grandson</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatAunt</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatGrandParent</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatGrandchild</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatGranddaughter</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatGrandfather</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatGrandmother</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatGrandson</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GreatUncle</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>HalfCousin</id>
      <def>Half cousins are the children of two half siblings.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Husband</id>
      <def>Definition: The role of a married man in relation to his wife.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>InLaw</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Marriage</id>
      <def>The formal union of a man and a woman, typically as recognized by law, by which they become husband and wife.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MaternalCousin</id>
      <def>specifies whether one individual is a cousin of another through the mother's side of the family </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Mother</id>
      <def>Definition: The family role of a woman in relation to her child or children</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>MotherInLaw</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Nephew</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Niece</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Parent</id>
      <def>Definition: A person’s father or mother</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PaternalCousin</id>
      <def>specifies whether one individual is a cousin of another through the father's side of the family </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>SecondCousin</id>
      <def>The children of two first cousins.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>SecondCousinOnceRemoved</id>
      <def>Two people for whom a second cousin relationship is one generation removed.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Sibling</id>
      <def>Definition: Each of two or more children or offspring having one or both parents in common</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Sister</id>
      <def>Definition: A woman or girl in relation to other daughters and sons of her parents</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>SisterInLaw</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Son</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Spouse</id>
      <def>BDLSS System: EMLODefinition: The role of a husband or wife, considered in relation to their partner.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>StepCousin</id>
      <def>Step-cousins are either stepchildren of an individual's aunt or uncle or nieces and nephews of one's step-parent.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ThirdCousin</id>
      <def>The grandchildren of two first cousins; also the children of two second cousins.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Uncle</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Wife</id>
      <def>Definition: Definition: The role of a married woman in relation to her husband.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>HoldPoliticalOffice</id>
      <def>Activity of someone holding a political office.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>RepresentativeAssembly</id>
      <def>A political institution in which a number of persons representing the population or privileged orders within the population of a state come together to debate, negotiate with the executive (originally the king or other ruler) and legislate. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AcademicSupervisor</id>
      <def>The role of a senior scientist or scholar who, along with their own responsibilities, aids and guides a postgraduate research student, or undergraduate student, in their research project; offering both moral support and scientific insight and guidance. The term is used in several countries for the doctoral advisor of a graduate student.http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supervisor#Academia</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Acquaintance</id>
      <def>The role of a person one knows slightly, but who is not a close friend.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AdministratorOfAcademicInstitution</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AdministratorOfInstitution</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Advocate</id>
      <def>The role of a person who publicly supports or recommends a particular cause or policy.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Attendee</id>
      <def>The role of a person who participates and is present at a conference or other gathering.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Author</id>
      <def>The role of someone who writes a book, article, or document.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Backer</id>
      <def>A person, institution, or country that supports someone or something, especially financially.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Buyer</id>
      <def>The role of a person who makes a purchase.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>CalledToBar</id>
      <def>The role of a person who is qualified to be allowed to argue in court on behalf of another party</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Chair</id>
      <def>The role of a person who acts as chairperson of who presides over (an organization, meeting, or public event).</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Child</id>
      <def>The role of a person in relation to his/her parents.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Collaborator</id>
      <def>The role of a person who works jointly on an activity or project; an associate.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Colleague</id>
      <def>The role of a person in relation to another person, who are both working within the same institution.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Conrector</id>
      <def>Administrator of a school (elementary, secondary), second in hierarchy after Director</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Contractee</id>
      <def>A party to a contract</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Contributor</id>
      <def>A person or thing that contributes something, in particular.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>CorrespondenceIntermediary</id>
      <def>A person who delivers or forwards a letter to the addressee on behalf of the author of the letter.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Correspondent</id>
      <def>The role of a person who writes letters on a regular basis.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Counsellor</id>
      <def>A person trained to give guidance on personal or psychological problems.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Creator</id>
      <def>The role of a person or thing that brings something into existence.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Dedicatee</id>
      <def>The role of an entity to whom something is dedicated</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DedicateeOfItem</id>
      <def>The role of an entity to whom an item is dedicated.
</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DedicateeOfWork</id>
      <def>The role of an entity to whom a creative work is dedicated.
</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Dedicator</id>
      <def>The role of a person who dedicates something to someone or something</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Director</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DisplacedPerson</id>
      <def>A person that participated in the enforced departure from his/her home, typically because of war, persecution, or natural disaster.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Disqualified</id>
      <def>The role of a person that is declared ineligible for an office, activity or competition because of an offence or infringement.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DisqualifiedFromOffice</id>
      <def>The role of a person that is declared ineligible for an office because of an offence or infringement</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Editor</id>
      <def>A person who is in charge of and determines the final content of a newspaper, magazine, or multi-author book.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Emigrant</id>
      <def>A person who leaves their own country in order to settle permanently in another country.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Employee</id>
      <def>a person employed for wages or salary, especially at non-executive level.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Employer</id>
      <def>a person or organization that employs people.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Engraver</id>
      <def>a skilled worker who can inscribe designs or writing onto a surface by carving or etching</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ExiledPerson</id>
      <def>A person who lives away from their native country, either from choice or compulsion.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Father</id>
      <def>The family role of a man in relation to his child or children</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Friend</id>
      <def>A person with whom one has a bond of mutual affection, typically one exclusive of sexual or family relations.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Funder</id>
      <def>The role of a person or organization who provide a person or organization with money for a particular purpose.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>FundsRecipient</id>
      <def>The role of something that receives funds</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Gift</id>
      <def>The role of a thing given willingly to someone without payment; a present.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GiftGiver</id>
      <def>The role of a person who gives a gift.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Giver</id>
      <def>The role of a person who gives something.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Guest</id>
      <def>The role of a person who is invited to visit someone's home or attend a particular social occasion.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Host</id>
      <def>The role of a person who receives or entertains other people as guests.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Housemate</id>
      <def>A person who shares a house with others.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Ilustrator</id>
      <def>a person who draws or creates pictures for magazines, books, advertising, etc.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Immigrant</id>
      <def>A person who comes to live permanently in a country that is not the person's native country.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Inscriber</id>
      <def>The role of a person who writes or carves (words or symbols) on something, especially as a formal or permanent record.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Instigator</id>
      <def>The role of a person who brings about or initiates something</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Intermediary</id>
      <def>The role of a person who acts as a link between people.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Interviewee</id>
      <def>A person who is interviewed by an interviewer in an interview ie who is questioned, consulted or evaluated by another person</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Interviewer</id>
      <def>A person who conducts an interview</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LetterAuthor</id>
      <def>The role of a person who writes a letter.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LetterRecipient</id>
      <def>The role of a person or thing that receives a letter.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LetterSender</id>
      <def>A person that sends a letter</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Member</id>
      <def>The role of a person, country, or organization that has joined a group, society, or team.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Mother</id>
      <def>The family role of a woman in relation to her child or children</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Owner</id>
      <def>The role of a person who owns something.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Parent</id>
      <def>a person's father or mother.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Participant</id>
      <def>The role of a person who takes part in something</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Patron</id>
      <def>A person who gives financial or other support to a person, organization, or cause.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Printer</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Publisher</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Recipient</id>
      <def>The role of a person or thing that receives or is awarded something.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Rector</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Refugee</id>
      <def>A person who has been forced to leave their country in order to escape war, persecution, or natural disaster.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Researcher</id>
      <def>The role of a person who undertakes a systematic investigation into and study of materials and sources in order to establish facts and reach new conclusion.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Resident</id>
      <def>A person who lives somewhere permanently or on a long-term basis.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Reviewer</id>
      <def>A person who writes critical appraisals of books, plays, films, etc. for publication.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Ruler</id>
      <def>A person exercising government or dominion</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Saloniste</id>
      <def>The role of a person who attends a salon (social gathering).</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Seller</id>
      <def>The role of a person who sells something.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Sender</id>
      <def>The role of a person who sends something, especially a letter by post</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Signatory</id>
      <def>The role of a party that has signed an agreement, especially a state that has signed a treaty.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Student</id>
      <def>A person who is studying at a university or other place of higher education.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Subrector</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Supervisor</id>
      <def>A person who supervises a person or an activity.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Trader</id>
      <def>A person who buys and sells goods, currency, or shares.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Translator</id>
      <def>The role of a person who translates from one language into another, especially as a profession.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>TravelCompanion</id>
      <def>A person who actively travels together with at least one other person.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Traveller</id>
      <def>A person who is travelling or who often travels.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Visitor</id>
      <def>The role of a person visiting someone or somewhere, especially socially or as a tourist.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Witness</id>
      <def>The role of a person who sees an event.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Acquaintanceship</id>
      <def>The context in which two people know each other slightly, but who are not  close friends</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AlbumAmicorum</id>
      <def>The first true autograph books that appeared in German and Dutch linguistic regions (possibly originating in Wittenberg) by the mid-16th century. Known as an album amicorum ("book of friends") or stammbuch ("friendship book").http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Autograph_book</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Audience</id>
      <def>A formal interview with a person in authority.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AudienceWithRuler</id>
      <def>A formal interview with a ruler i.e. a person exercising government or dominion.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Collaboration</id>
      <def>Activity of working together to do a task and to achieve shared goals</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Contract</id>
      <def>A written or spoken agreement, especially one concerning employment, sales, or tenancy, that is intended to be enforceable by law.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ContractActivity</id>
      <def>The activity that consists of a written or spoken agreement  that is intended to be enforceable by law.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ContractDocument</id>
      <def>A document containing a written representation of a contract</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Correspondence</id>
      <def>an activity where one person writes a letter to another person.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Dedication</id>
      <def>An inscription or form of words dedicating a building, book, etc. to a person or deity</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DedicationActivity</id>
      <def>The activity of addressing or inscribing (a literary work, for example) to another as a mark of respect or affection.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DedicationOfItem</id>
      <def>To address or inscribe an item to another as a mark of respect or affection.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>DedicationOfWork</id>
      <def>To address or inscribe a literary work to another as a mark of respect or affection.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Document</id>
      <def>A piece of written, printed, or electronic matter that provides information or evidence or that serves as an official record.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>ExchangeOccasionalVerse</id>
      <def>An activity where one person authors verse and sends it to another person. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Friendship</id>
      <def> a relationship of mutual affection between two or more people. Friendship is a stronger form of interpersonal bond than an association. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>GiftGiving</id>
      <def>This context describes the activity of giving and receiving a gift.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>InclusionAlbumAmicorum</id>
      <def>An activity where a personl includes a creative work in an Album Amicorum</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Inscription</id>
      <def>Writing or carving (words or symbols) on something, especially as a formal or permanent record., as on a monument or in a book</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Interview</id>
      <def>A formal meeting in which one or more persons question, consult, or evaluate another person</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Introduction</id>
      <def>The context of one person being introduced to another person by way of a third person who acts as an intermediary. </def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Journey</id>
      <def>The activity of travelling from one place to another.

Travel is the movement of people between relatively distant geographical locations, and can involve travel by foot, bicycle, automobile, train, boat, airplane, or other means, with or without luggage, and can be one way or round trip.

Travel can also include relatively short stays between successive movements.https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Travel</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Letter</id>
      <def>A written, typed, or printed communication, sent in an envelope by post or messenger.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>LiteraryExchange</id>
      <def>An activity that involves the exchange between two people of a literary creative work, e.g. a book.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Meeting</id>
      <def>Activity when two or more people meet, by chance or arrangement</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Salon</id>
      <def>A regular social gathering, especially of writers and artists</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>SocialContactRole</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>SocialGathering</id>
      <def>A gathering for the purpose of promoting fellowship</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>SocialVisit</id>
      <def>The activity of going to see and spend time with (someone) socially</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Trade</id>
      <def>Trade is to transfer the ownership of goods from one person or entity to another by getting something in exchange from the buyer.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Transmission</id>
      <def>the action or process of transmitting something or the state of being transmitted</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Verse</id>
      <def>Writing arranged with a metrical rhythm, typically having a rhyme.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Writing</id>
      <def>A sequence of letters, words, or symbols marked on a surface.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Ennoble</id>
      <def>The activity of making someone a member of the nobility.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Audience</id>
      <def/>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>AudienceMember</id>
      <def>A person who is one of the assembled spectators or listeners at a public event such as a play, film, concert, or meeting.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>InauguralSpeech</id>
      <def>A speech delivered at an inaugural ceremony</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>PublicEvent</id>
      <def>A public event such as a play, film, concert, or meeting.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Speaker</id>
      <def>A person who delivers a speech or lecture.</def>
   </field>
   <field>
      <id>Speech</id>
      <def>A formal address or discourse delivered to an audience.</def>
   </field>
</fields>
